Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- People Files, 1960-1964; Series B
  - Barnabas--Barnes, Zane, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/14)
  - Barnett--Barry, Gail, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 47/15)
  - Barry, Gene--Bartle, 196 (Box-folder 47/16)
  - Bartlett--Baruch, Jerome, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/1)
  - Bas--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 48/2)
  - Bat--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 48/3)
  - Baucom, Ella--Baugartner, B.C., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/4)
  - Baum, David--Bautista, Constantino, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/5)
  - Baw--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 48/6)
  - Bax--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 48/7)
  - Bay--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 48/8)
  - Baz--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 48/9)
  - Bea--Bean, L.E., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/10)
  - Bean, Ormond R.--Bearchum, Sophia, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 48/11)
  - Beard, James--Beaver, Patricia, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 48/12)
  - Beb--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 48/13)
  - Bec--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/14)
  - Bed--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 48/15)
  - Bee-, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 48/16)
  - Beg--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 48/17)
  - Beh--, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 48/18)
  - Bei--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 48/19)
  - Bejarabo, Patricia, 1963 (Box-folder 48/20)
  - Beksvoort, Harry W., 1963 (Box-folder 48/21)
  - Belafonte--Bell, Keith, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Bell, Larry--Belton, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/2)
  - Bemelmans, 1962 (Box-folder 49/3)
  - Bender--Benner, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Bennett, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Benning--Benton, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/6)
  - Bera--Bergh, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/7)
  - Bergholz--Bernards, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/8)
  - Berne--Bertsch, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/9)
  - Bes--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 49/10)
  - Bet--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/11)
  - Bev--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 49/12)
  - Beu--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 49/13)
  - Bey--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 49/14)
  - Bezich, 1961 (Box-folder 49/15)
  - Biancone, 1963 (Box-folder 50/1)
  - Bible, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 50/2)
  - Bic--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 50/3)
  - Bid--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/4)
  - Bie--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 50/5)
  - Big--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 50/6)
  - Binford, 1963 (Box-folder 50/7)
  - Bikel, 1963 (Box-folder 50/8)
  - Bill--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/9)
  - Bin--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/10)
  - Bionda, 1961 (Box-folder 50/11)
  - Bir--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 50/12)
  - Bis--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/13)
  - Bit--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 50/14)
  - Bixby, 1963 (Box-folder 50/15)
  - Bizon, Mike, 1964 (Box-folder 50/16)
  - Bja--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 50/17)
  - Black--Blaesing, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 50/18)
  - Blaine--Blake, Loren, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/19)
  - Blake, Maxine--Blanchard, Kathy, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/20)
  - Blanchard, Sandy--Blaylock, Molly, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 50/21)
  - Ble--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 50/22)
  - Bli--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/23)
  - Blo--, 1959; 1961-1964 (Box-folder 50/24)
  - Blu--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 51/1)
  - Blyth, Bonnie, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 51/2)
  - Boa--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 51/3)
  - Bob--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 51/4)
  - Boc--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 51/5)
  - Bod--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 51/6)
  - Boe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 51/7)
  - Bog--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 51/8)
  - Boh--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 51/9)
  - Boi--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 51/10)
  - Bojinoff, John, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 51/11)
  - Bokemeier, Janet, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 51/12)
  - Boland--Bolger, Mary Lynn, 1960; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 51/13)
  - Bolger, Ray--Bolton, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 51/14)
  - Bon--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 51/15)
  - Boo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 51/16)
  - Boq--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 51/17)
  - Bor--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 51/18)
  - Bos--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 51/19)
  - Bot--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 51/20)
  - Bou--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 51/21)
  - Bowe--Barnes, William A., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Bowes, William E.--Bowmer, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Boxco, 1961 (Box-folder 52/3)
  - Boy--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/4)
  - Boz--, 1961 (Box-folder 52/5)
  - Braaten--Bradford, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 52/6)
  - Bradley--Brandis, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/7)
  - Brando--Brazzi, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Breall--Breese, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 52/9)
  - Brehm--Brezhnev, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/10)
  - Brice--Bright, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/11)
  - Brill--Brinkman, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 52/12)
  - Brissenden--Brixey, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 52/13)
  - Broadbent--Brooker, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Brooks--Brous, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 53/2)
  - Brower--Brown, Doris, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Brown, E. A.--Brown, Harold, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/4)
  - Brown, Harrison--Brown, Pieter, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Brown, Robert--Brown, Willie, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/6)
  - Browne--Brownton, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/7)
  - Bru--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 53/8)
  - Bry--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 53/9)
  - Bubalo, 1964 (Box-folder 53/10)
  - Buchanan--Buck, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/1)
  - Buckallow--Buczkowski, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/2)
  - Bue--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Buf--, 1964 (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Bugbee, 1963 (Box-folder 54/5)
  - Buhite, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 54/6)
  - Buker, 1962 (Box-folder 54/7)
  - Bul--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/8)
  - Bum--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 54/9)
  - Bun--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/10)
  - Buol, 1963 (Box-folder 54/11)
  - Burcaw--Burgoyne, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/12)
  - Burke--Burkhardt, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/13)
  - Burkheimer--Burnie, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/14)
  - Burns--Burr, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/15)
  - Burrell--Burton, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/16)
  - Bus--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/17)
  - But--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 54/18)
  - Buxton, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 54/19)
  - Buyas, 1961 (Box-folder 54/20)
  - Buzzetti, undated (Box-folder 54/21)
  - Bybee, 1961 (Box-folder 54/22)
  - Bye--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/23)
  - Byington, 1962 (Box-folder 54/24)
  - Byr--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 54/25)
  - Cab--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Cadigan, 1961 (Box-folder 55/2)
  - Cal--, 1962 (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Cage, 1962 (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Cah--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Cai--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Cake, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 55/7)
  - Calavan--Callan, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Callas-Calvin, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 55/9)
  - Cambric--Campbell, Don, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Campbell, Elizabeth--Camus, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/11)
  - Can--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/12)
  - Cao, Thi Hue, 1961 (Box-folder 55/13)
  - Cap--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/14)
  - Caramanica--Carlos, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/15)
  - Carlsen--Carmann, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/16)
  - Carmel--Carpenter, Virgil, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 55/17)
  - Carpenter, M. Scott, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 56/1)
  - Carpenter, M. Scott, 1962 (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Carper--Carson, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 56/3)
  - Carstensen--Cary, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 56/4)
  - Cas--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Cat--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Cav--Cau, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Caw--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Cay--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Cec--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Cedergreen, 1962 (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Ceglar, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 56/12)
  - Cel--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 56/13)
  - Cer--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 56/14)
  - Cha--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 56/15)
  - Cha--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 56/16-17)
  - Che--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Chh--, 1962 (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Chi--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Cho--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Chr--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/5)
  - Chu--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 57/6)
  - Ciappini, 1964 (Box-folder 57/7)
  - Cieplinski, 1961 (Box-folder 57/8)
  - Cio--, 1962 (Box-folder 57/9)
  - Citron, 1963 (Box-folder 57/10)
  - Cla--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 57/11)
  - Cla--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 57/12)
  - Cla--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/13)
  - Cle--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 57/14)
  - Cli--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 57/15)
  - Cliburn, Van, 1963 (Box-folder Oversize B1/13)
  - Clo--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 57/16)
  - Clu--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 57/17)
  - Cly--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 57/18)
  - Coa--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 57/19)
  - Cob--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/20)
  - Coc--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 57/21)
  - Cod--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 57/22)
  - Coe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 57/23)
  - Cof--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 57/24)
  - Cog--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 58/1)
  - Coburn, 1961 (Box-folder 58/2)
  - Coh-- (part 1), 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/3)
  - Coh-- (part 2), 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/4)
  - Coker, 1960 (Box-folder 58/5)
  - Colas--Colby, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 58/6)
  - Cole, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Coleman--Collings, Julia, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/8)
  - Collins, Leroy--Colvin, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/9)
  - Com--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 58/10)
  - Condor--Conley, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/11)
  - Connally--Connors, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 58/12)
  - Conoway--Conyers, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 58/13)
  - Cook--Cook, John, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/14)
  - Cook, Nancy--Cooley, Spade, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 58/15)
  - Cooley, William--Cooper, John, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Cooper, L. Gordon, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Cop--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Coram--Corbett, Alfred, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Corbett, Alice--Cordle, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Cordova--Corwin, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Cos--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 59/7)
  - Cot--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 59/8)
  - Cou--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 59/9)
  - Cov--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 59/10)
  - Cow--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 59/11)
  - Cox--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 59/12)
  - Coy--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 59/13)
  - Coz--, 1963 (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Crabb--Craig, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Crain--Cranston, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Crawford, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Cri--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 60/5)
  - Cre--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 60/6)
  - Cro--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60/7-8)
  - Cru--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 60/9)
  - Cud--, 1961 (Box-folder 60/10)
  - Cuelke, 1960 (Box-folder 60/11)
  - Cugat, 1962 (Box-folder 60/12)
  - Cui, 1963 (Box-folder 60/13)
  - Cul--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 60/14)
  - Cum--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 60/15)
  - Cun--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 60/16)
  - Cup--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 60/17)
  - Cur--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 60/18)
  - Cus--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 60/19)
  - Cut--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 60/20)
  - Cyders, 1963 (Box-folder 60/21)
  - Czarnowsky, 1963 (Box-folder 60/22)
  - Czuba, 1962 (Box-folder 60/23)
  - Czyzewski, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 60/24)
  - Daack, 1962 (Box-folder 61/1)
  - Dabney, 1962 (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Dac--, 1962 (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Dadey, 1964 (Box-folder 61/4)
  - Dag--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 61/5)
  - Dah--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/6)
  - Dai--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 61/7)
  - Dakins, 1964 (Box-folder 61/8)
  - Dal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/9)
  - Dam--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 61/10)
  - Dan--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/11)
  - Dan--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 61/12)
  - Dao--, 1961 (Box-folder 61/13)
  - Dar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/14)
  - Das--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/15)
  - Dau--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 61/16)
  - Dav--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/17)
  - Dav--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/18)
  - Davis, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 61/19-22)
  - Daw--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - Day--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Day--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/3)
  - Dea--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/4)
  - Deb--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/5)
  - Dec--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Dee--, 1961--1962 (Box-folder 62/7)
  - Def--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/8)
  - Deg--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 62/9)
  - Deh--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/10)
  - Dei--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/11)
  - Def--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 62/12)
  - Ddek--, 1962 (Box-folder 62/13)
  - Del--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/14)
  - Dem--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/15)
  - Dem--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 62/16)
  - Den--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/17)
  - Dep--, 1962 (Box-folder 62/18)
  - Der--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 62/19)
  - Des--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 62/20)
  - Det--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 63/1)
  - Deu--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 63/2)
  - Dev--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/3)
  - Dew--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 63/4)
  - Dexter, 1963 (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Dey--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 63/6)
  - Dezendorf, 1962 (Box-folder 63/7)
  - Dhein, 1960 (Box-folder 63/8)
  - Dhutiyabhodhi, 1961 (Box-folder 63/9)
  - Dia--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/10)
  - Dib--, 1963 (Box-folder 63/11)
  - Dic--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/12)
  - Dic--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 63/13)
  - Did--, 1963 (Box-folder 63/14)
  - Die--Dif, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/15)
  - Dig, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 63/16)
  - Dil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/17)
  - Dim--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 63/18)
  - Din--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 63/19)
  - Dio--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 63/20)
  - Di Pasquale, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 63/21)
  - Dir--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 63/22)
  - Dis--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 63/23)
  - Dit--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 63/24)
  - Divinl, 1961 (Box-folder 63/25)
  - Dix--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 63/26)
  - Doa--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 63/27)
  - Dizney, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 63/28)
  - Dob--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/1)
  - Doc--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 64/2)
  - Dod--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 64/3)
  - Doe--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 64/4)
  - Doh--, 1961 (Box-folder 64/5)
  - Doi--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 64/6)
  - Dol--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 64/7)
  - Dom--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 64/8)
  - Don--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/9)
  - Don--, 1961-964 (Box-folder 64/10)
  - Doo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/11)
  - Dor--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 64/12)
  - os--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 64/13)
  - Dot--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 64/14)
  - Dou--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 64/15)
  - Dou--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/16)
  - Dove, 1962 (Box-folder 64/17)
  - Dow--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/18)
  - Doy--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 64/19)
  - Dozono, 1961 (Box-folder 64/20)
  - Dra--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 64/21)
  - Dre--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 65/1)
  - Dri--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 65/2)
  - Dro--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/3)
  - Dru--, 1960; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Dry--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 65/5)
  - Duall, 1963 (Box-folder 65/6)
  - Dub--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/7)
  - Duc--, 1962 (Box-folder 65/8)
  - Dud--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/9)
  - Due--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 65/10)
  - Duf--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 65/11)
  - Dug--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 65/12)
  - Duhrkoop, 1962 (Box-folder 65/13)
  - Duk--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/14)
  - Dulles, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 65/15)
  - Dum--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 65/16)
  - Dun--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 65/17)
  - Dun--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/18)
  - Dup--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 65/19)
  - Dur--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 65/20)
  - Dus--, 1963 (Box-folder 65/21)
  - Dut--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 65/22)
  - Duus, 1960 (Box-folder 65/23)
  - Duvall, 1964 (Box-folder 65/24)
  - Duzieme, undated (Box-folder 65/25)
  - Dvorak, 1962 (Box-folder 65/26)
  - Dwight, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 65/27)
  - Dwy--, 196101964 (Box-folder 65/28)
  - Dyar, 1961 (Box-folder 65/29)
  - Dybwad, 1963 (Box-folder 65/30)
  - Dye--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 65/31)
  - Dyk--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 65/32)
  - Dyr, 1960 (Box-folder 65/33)
  - Dyson, 1963 (Box-folder 65/34)
  - Eades, 1962 (Box-folder 65/35)
  - Eag--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/1)
  - Eames, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Ear--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/3)
  - Eas--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Eat--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Ebaka, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Ebe--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 66/7)
  - Ecc--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/8)
  - Echeverria, 1961 (Box-folder 66/9)
  - Eck--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/10)
  - Eco--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 66/11)
  - Edd--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 66/12)
  - Ede--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/13)
  - Edg--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/14)
  - Edlefsen, 1961 (Box-folder 66/15)
  - Edm--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/16)
  - Edner, 1961 (Box-folder 66/17)
  - Eds--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 66/18)
  - Edw--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 66/19)
  - Edw--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/20)
  - Effinger, 1962 (Box-folder 66/21)
  - Ega--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 66/22)
  - Egbert, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 66/23)
  - Ege--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 66/24)
  - Egg--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 66/25)
  - Egn--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 66/26)
  - Ehara, 1961 (Box-folder 66/27)
  - Ehelebe, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 66/28)
  - Ehl--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 66/29)
  - Ehmann, 1963 (Box-folder 66/30)
  - Ehr--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 66/31)
  - Eic--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 66/32)
  - Eigner, 1964 (Box-folder 66/33)
  - Eilts, 1963 (Box-folder 66/34)
  - Eiman, 1960 (Box-folder 66/35)
  - Einaudi, 1961 (Box-folder 66/36)
  - Eis--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 66/37)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 66/38)
  - Eitner, 1964 (Box-folder 66/39)
  - Eiviers, 1962 (Box-folder 67/1)
  - Ekberg, 1962 (Box-folder 67/2)
  - Ekebald, 1961 (Box-folder 67/3)
  - Ekholm, 1964 (Box-folder 67/4)
  - Ekter, 1963 (Box-folder 67/5)
  - Ela--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 67/6)
  - Elbrick, 1961 (Box-folder 67/7)
  - Eld--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 67/8)
  - Elf--, 1964 (Box-folder 67/9)
  - Elg--, 1963 (Box-folder 67/10)
  - Eli--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/11)
  - Elk--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 67/12)
  - Ely, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 67/13)
  - Ell--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/14)
  - Ell--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 67/15)
  - Ell--, 1964 (Box-folder 67/16)
  - Elman, 1962 (Box-folder 67/17)
  - Els--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 67/18)
  - Elt--, 1960; 1964 (Box-folder 67/19)
  - Elwell, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 67/20)
  - Emakiser, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 67/21)
  - Eme--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 67/22)
  - Emigh, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 67/23)
  - Emm--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/24)
  - Emp--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 67/25)
  - Ems--, 1962 (Box-folder 67/26)
  - Endre, 1963 (Box-folder 67/27)
  - Eng--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/28)
  - Eng--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 67/29)
  - Enn--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 67/30)
  - Eno--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 67/31)
  - Enquist, 1962 (Box-folder 67/32)
  - Ent--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 67/33)
  - Enz--, undated (Box-folder 67/34)
  - Eoff, 1962 (Box-folder 67/35)
  - Epley, 1962 (Box-folder 67/36)
  - Epp--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67/37)
  - Epstein, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 67/38)
  - Epton, 1964 (Box-folder 67/39)
  - Erd--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 67/40)
  - Erfeldt, 1962 (Box-folder 67/41)
  - Erhard, Ludwig, 1962 (Box-folder 67/42)
  - Eri--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/43)
  - Erl--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 67/44)
  - Ern--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 67/45)
  - Ersland, 1961 (Box-folder 67/46)
  - Ertz, 1962 (Box-folder 67/47)
  - Erv--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 67/48)
  - Erw--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 68/1)
  - Esar, 1961 (Box-folder 68/2)
  - Esc--, 1961-1962; 19646 (Box-folder 68/3)
  - Esh--, 1964 (Box-folder 68/4)
  - Esiminger, 1964 (Box-folder 68/5)
  - Esp--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 68/6)
  - Est--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 68/7)
  - Eth--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 68/8)
  - Etling, undated (Box-folder 68/9)
  - Eubanks, 1963 (Box-folder 68/10)
  - Euwer, 1963 (Box-folder 68/11)
  - Eva--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 68/12)
  - Eve--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 68/13)
  - Evick, 1963 (Box-folder 68/14)
  - Evjen, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 68/15)
  - Ewa--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 68/16)
  - Ewe, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 68/17)
  - Ewi, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 68/18)
  - Exe--, 1963 (Box-folder 68/19)
  - Exner, 1962 (Box-folder 68/20)
  - Extra, 1963 (Box-folder 68/21)
  - Eye--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 68/22)
  - Eyler, 1964 (Box-folder 68/23)
  - Eymann, 1961 (Box-folder 68/24)
  - Eyr--, 1961 (Box-folder 68/25)
  - Ezekoli, 1964 (Box-folder 68/26)
  - Fab--, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 68/27)
  - Fac--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 68/28)
  - Fad--, 1961 (Box-folder 68/29)
  - Fag--, 1963 (Box-folder 68/30)
  - Fah--, 1963 (Box-folder 68/31)
  - Fai--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 68/32)
  - Fal--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 68/33)
  - Fan--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 68/34)
  - Far--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 68/35)
  - Far--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 68/36)
  - Fas--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 68/37)
  - Fat--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68/38)
  - Fau--, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 68/39)
  - Fav--, 1964 (Box-folder 68/40)
  - Fay--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 68/41)
  - Faz--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68/42)
  - Fea--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 69/1)
  - Fed--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 69/2)
  - Fee--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 69/3)
  - Fei--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/4)
  - Fel--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/5)
  - Fen--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 69/6)
  - Fer--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 69/7)
  - Fes--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 69/8)
  - Fet--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 69/9)
  - Fev--, 1960 (Box-folder 69/10)
  - Fey, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 69/11)
  - Fid--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69/12)
  - Fie--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/13)
  - Fir--, 1963 (Box-folder 69/14)
  - Fig--, 1963 (Box-folder 69/15)
  - Fik--, 1962 (Box-folder 69/16)
  - Fil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/17)
  - Fin--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/18)
  - Fir--, 1961 (Box-folder 69/19)
  - Fis--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/20)
  - Fis--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 69/21)
  - Fit--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/22)
  - Fix--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 69/23)
  - Fjellman, 1963 (Box-folder 69/24)
  - Fla--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/25)
  - Fle--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 69/26)
  - Fli--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 70/1)
  - Flo--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 70/2)
  - Flynn, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 70/3)
  - Fog--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 70/4)
  - Fol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 70/5)
  - Fon--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 70/6)
  - Foote, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 70/7)
  - For--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 70/8)
  - For--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 70/9)
  - For--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 70/10)
  - Fos--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Fou--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 70/12)
  - Fow--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 70/13)
  - Fox, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 70/14)
  - Foy, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70/15)
  - Foz, 1962 (Box-folder 70/16)
  - Fra--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 71/1)
  - Fra--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71/2)
  - Fra--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 71/3)
  - Fra--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 71/4)
  - Fre--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 71/5)
  - Fre--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 71/6)
  - Fri--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 71/7)
  - Fro--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 71/8)
  - Fruechtel, 1962 (Box-folder 71/9)
  - Fry--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 71/10)
  - Fuchs, 1962 (Box-folder 71/11)
  - Fue--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 71/12)
  - Fugle, 1963 (Box-folder 71/13)
  - Fuh--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 71/14)
  - Fujita, 1962 (Box-folder 71/15)
  - Ful--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 71/16)
  - Fun--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 71/17)
  - Fur--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 72/1)
  - Fuqua, Linda, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72/2)
  - Fyfe, Gordon, 1962 (Box-folder 72/3)
  - Gab--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/4)
  - Gad--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 72/5)
  - Gaeller, 1962 (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Gag--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72/7)
  - Gai--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/8)
  - Gal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/9)
  - Gam--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/10)
  - Gan--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 72/11)
  - Gar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/12)
  - Gar--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 72/13)
  - Gas--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/14)
  - Gat--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 72/15)
  - Gau--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 72/16)
  - Gav--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 72/17)
  - Gay--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 72/18)
  - Gaz--, 1961 (Box-folder 72/19)
  - Gea--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 72/20)
  - Geb--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 72/21)
  - Ged--, 1964 (Box-folder 72/22)
  - Geer, 1962 (Box-folder 72/23)
  - Geh--, 1964 (Box-folder 72/24)
  - Gei--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 72/25)
  - Gel--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 72/26)